A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Legislation, 1958-1981
  - 94th Congress, 1975-1976 (Box not specified)
    - HR 7750—Amendment, Copyright Act of 1909 (Box 13:, Folder 610-612)
    - HR 8095—Production of Housing (Box 13:, Folder 613)
    - HR 8436—Wild and Scenic Rivers Act, Housatonic River (Box 13:, Folder 614)
    - HR 8669—Disposal of Surplus Properties to States and Cities (Box 13:, Folder 615)
    - HR 8979—Rail Act, Percentage of Federal Subsidies (Box 13:, Folder 616)
    - HR 9103—Public Financing of Congressional Elections (Box 13:, Folder 617)
    - HR 9189—Veterans pensions, WWI (Box 13:, Folder 618)
    - HR 9744—Amendment, OSHA, Loans to Local Governments (Box 13:, Folder 619)
    - HR 9850—Conservation and Management of Fisheries (Box 14:, Folder 620-621)
    - HR 10171—National Commission on Regulatory Reform (Box 14:, Folder 622-623)
    - HR 11794—Congressional Disapproval of Executive Agency Policies (Box 14:, Folder 624)
    - HR 12059—See HR 8669 (Box 14:, Folder 625)
    - HR 15100—National Diabetes Advisory Board (Box 14:, Folder 626)
    - HR 15422—Wild and Scenic Rivers Act (Box 14:, Folder 627)
    - HConRes 89—911 Telephone Number (Box 14:, Folder 628)
    - HConRes 98—Martin Luther King Statute for Capitol (Box 14:, Folder 629)
    - HConRes 190—Release of Ukrainian Intellectuals (Box 14:, Folder 630)
    - HConRes 205—Resurrection of Ukrainian Catholic and Orthodox Churches (Box 14:, Folder 631)
    - HConRes 471—Every Person Held in Slavery Considered a U.S. citizen (Box 14:, Folder 632)
    - HRes 138—Select Committee on Intelligence (Box 14:, Folder 633)
    - HRes 222—Relief of John Egan (Box 14:, Folder 634)
    - HRes 269—Press Coverage of 94th Congress (Box 14:, Folder 635)
    - HRes 404—Jan 22, Ukrainian Independence Day (Box 14:, Folder 636)
    - HRes 681—Disapproval of Expulsion of Israel from the U.N. (Box 14:, Folder 637)
    - HRes 804—Condemn U.N. Resolution Equating Zionism with Racism (Box 14:, Folder 638)
    - HRes 985—Termination of Aid to Angola (Box 14:, Folder 639)
    - HRes 1298—House Committee on Intelligence (Box 14:, Folder 640)
    - HRes 1310—Opposition to Closing of Post Offices (Box 14:, Folder 641)
    - HRes 1322—Telecommunications Policy (Box 14:, Folder 642-643)
    - HRes 1566—Condemn Murders of Orlando Letillier and Roni Moffitt (Box 14:, Folder 644)
    - HRes 1574—Reduction of House Committee Meetings (Box 14:, Folder 645)
    - HJRes 130—Prohibit Fees on Oil Imports (Box 14:, Folder 646)
    - HJRes 155—Honor the Connecticut Bar Association (Box 14:, Folder 647)
    - HJRes 201—Joint Committee on Classified Information (Box 14:, Folder 648)
    - HJRes 608—Atlantic Conference (Box 14:, Folder 649)
    - HJRes 640—National St. Elizabeth Seaton Day (Box 14:, Folder 650)
    - HJRes 693—National Family Week (Box 14:, Folder 651)
  - 95th Congress, 1977-1978
    - HR 1502—Solar Energy Loan Administration (Box 14:, Folder 652)
    - HR 1808—WWI Veterans Pensions (Box 14:, Folder 653)
    - HR 2364—Damages, Oil Pollution (Box 14:, Folder 654)
    - HR 2518—Youth Camp Safety (Box 14:, Folder 655)
    - HR 3216—Relief of Roger Boyd (Box 14:, Folder 656)
    - HR 3669—Assure Natural Gas for Consumers (Box 14:, Folder 657)
    - HR 4125—Equalize Treatment of Craft and Industrial Workers in Construction (Box 14:, Folder 658-661)
    - HR 4234—Disclosure of Information of Personal Finances (Box 14:, Folder 662)
    - HR 4368—Social Security Act, Eligible Drugs (Box 14:, Folder 663)
    - HR 4515—Collective Bargaining for Postal Employees (Box 14:, Folder 664)
    - HR 4628—Public Investments, Secretary of the Treasury (Box 15:, Folder 665)
    - HR 4949—Financial Disclosure Act (Box 15:, Folder 666)
    - HR 5592—Saccharin Ban (Box 15:, Folder 667)
    - HR 5641—Energy Conservation, Electric Vehicles (Box 15:, Folder 668)
    - HR 5818—Accelerated Depreciation Allowance Act (Box 15:, Folder 669)
    - HR 5930—Relief of John J. Egan (Box 15:, Folder 670)
    - HR 6171—Campaign Financing Reform Act (Box 15:, Folder 671)
    - HR 6868—Public Disclosure of Lobbying (Box 15:, Folder 672)
    - HR 9061—Census Reform (Box 15:, Folder 673)
    - HR 9129—Amendment, Federal Property and Administrative Services Act (Box 15:, Folder 674)
    - HR 9712—Long Island Sound Heritage (Box 15:, Folder 675)
    - HR 10421—Legislative Oversight Act (Box 15:, Folder 676)
    - HR 10423—Elimination of Racketeering in Cigarette Sales (Box 15:, Folder 677)
    - HR 10756—Rescind Budget Authority, Presidential Message 27 Jan 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 678)
    - HR 10757 (Box 15:, Folder 679)
    - HR 10758 (Box 15:, Folder 680)
    - HR 11270—Income Tax, Unmarried Individuals (Box 15:, Folder 681)
    - HR 12954—Rescind Budget Authority, Presidential Message 12 May 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 682)
    - HR 13010—Rescind Budget Authority, Presidential Message 5 Jun 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 683)
    - HR 13565—Rescind Budget Authority, Presidential Message 20 Jul 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 684)
    - HR 13609—Permit National Banks to Underwrite State/Local Securities (Box 15:, Folder 685)
    - HR 13760—Promote Amateur Athletic Abilities (Box 15:, Folder 686)
    - HR 13805—Repeal IRS Provision Concerning Withholding a Portion of Lottery winnings (Box 15:, Folder 687)
    - HConRes 110—Revise Congressional Budget FY77 (Box 15:, Folder 688)
    - HConRes 160—Harassment of Soviet Jews (Box 15:, Folder 689)
    - HConRes 165—Rights of Ukrainian Citizens (Box 15:, Folder 690)
    - HConRes 195—1978 Budget (Box 15:, Folder 691)
    - HConRes 214—Congressional Budget FY 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 692)
    - HConRes 341—Revision Congressional Budget 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 693)
    - HConRes 385—Detention of Mykola Rudenko and Oleska Tykhy (Box 15:, Folder 694)
    - HConRes 513—Condemnation of PLO Terrorism (Box 15:, Folder 695)
    - HConRes 559—Budget FY79 (Box 15:, Folder 696)
    - HConRes 610—Condemnation of Kidnapping of Aldo Moro (Box 15:, Folder 697)
    - HConRes 616—Denunciation of Murder of Aldo Moro (Box 15:, Folder 698)
    - HConRes 648—Denunciation of American Nazi Party Rally (Box 15:, Folder 699)
    - HConRes 683—Revision, Congressional Budget FY79 (Box 15:, Folder 700)
    - HConRes 684—Seabrook, NH Nuclear Power Plant (Box 15:, Folder 701)
    - HRes 72—Select Commission of Population (Box 15:, Folder 702)
    - HRes 349—Select Committee on Welfare Reorganization (Box 15:, Folder 703)
    - HRes 372—House Commission on Congressional Operations (Box 15:, Folder 704)
    - HRes 479—Requirement that Congressional Record Contain Verbatim Remarks (Box 15:, Folder 705)
    - HRes 788—Commission on Domestic and International Hunger (Box 15:, Folder 706)
    - HRes 1082—Condemnation of Assassination of Aldo Moro (Box 15:, Folder 707)
    - HRes 1167—Honor Bob Hope's 75th Birthday (Box 15:, Folder 708)
    - HRes 1314—Transfer of 1980 Olympics from Moscow (Box 15:, Folder 709)
    - HRes 1334—Urging Sun Myung Moon to Appear Before the Subcommittee on International Organizations Investigating Korean-American Relations (Box 15:, Folder 710)
    - HRes 1360 (Box 15:, Folder 711)
    - HRes 1369 (Box 15:, Folder 712)
    - HRes 1387 (Box 15:, Folder 713)
    - HRes 1394 (Box 15:, Folder 714)
    - HRes 1401—Contribution of Bernardo de Galvez to U.S. Independence (Box 15:, Folder 715)
    - HRes 1442—See HRes 1334 (Box 15:, Folder 716)
    - HJRes 399—United States Space Observance (Box 15:, Folder 717)
    - HJRes 501—National Family Week (Box 15:, Folder 718)
    - HJRes 788—Education Day, USA (Box 15:, Folder 719)
    - HJRes 811 (Box 15:, Folder 720)
    - HJRes 820—Museum Day (Box 15:, Folder 721)
    - HJRes 933—National Grandparents' Day (Box 15:, Folder 722)
    - HJRes 946—National Guard Day (Box 15:, Folder 723)
    - HJRes 950—National Family Week (Box 15:, Folder 724)
    - HJRes 999—National Port Week (Box 15:, Folder 725)
    - HJRes 1007—Asian/Pacific American Week (Box 15:, Folder 726)
    - HJRes 1014—Remembrance of Victims of the Holocaust (Box 15:, Folder 727)
    - HJRes 1030—National Brotherhood Day (Box 15:, Folder 728)
    - HJRes 1076—National Guard Day (Box 15:, Folder 729)
    - HJRes 1149—Vietnam Veterans Week (Box 15:, Folder 730)
    - 95th Congress Legislative Summary (Box 15:, Folder 731)
  - 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box not specified)
    - HR 1—Federal Financing of Congressional Election (Box 16:, Folder 732)
    - HR 39—Alaska Land Grants Conservation Act (Box 16:, Folder 733-734)
    - HR 65—Sunset Act (Box 16:, Folder 735)
    - HR 1539—Municipal bank revenue underwritings (Box 16:, Folder 736)
    - HR 997—Sound Recording Performance Rights Amendments (Box 16:, Folder 737)
    - HR 1554—Relief of John J. Egan (Box 16:, Folder 738)
    - HR 1555—Relief of Roger Boyd, Jr. (Box 16:, Folder 739)
    - HR 2180-2189—Recision Bills (Box 16:, Folder 740)
    - HR 2249—Terminate Dickey-Lincoln Project (Box 16:, Folder 741-742)
    - HR 2443—Law Enforcement Officers Bill of Rights (Box 16:, Folder 743)
    - HR 2792—Condominium Act of 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 744)
    - HR 3562—Withholding Tax on Lottery Winnings (Box 16:, Folder 745)
    - HR 3609—Tax, Unmarried Individuals (Box 16:, Folder 746)
    - HR 3786—Small Hydroelectric Projects (Box 16:, Folder 747)
    - HR 3826—Long Island Sound Heritage (Box 16:, Folder 748)
    - HR 4146—Congressional Medal of Honor, Vincent Pantozzi (Box 16:, Folder 749)
    - HR 4293—Gold Medal in Recognition of Matthew Alexander Henson (Box 16:, Folder 750)
    - HR 4347—Diabetes Research Act (Box 16:, Folder 751)
    - HR 4459—Filippo Mazzei Stamp (Box 16:, Folder 752)
    - HR 4970—Campaign Financing (Box 16:, Folder 753)
    - HR 4986—Depository Institutions Deregulation Act (Box 16:, Folder 754)
    - HR 5209—Tax Deductions for Solar Energy (Box 16:, Folder 755)
    - HR 5674—Rescind Budget Authority, 1 October 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 756)
    - HR 5683—Federal Credit Program Control Act (Box 16:, Folder 757)
    - HR 5858—Sunset Review Act (Box 16:, Folder 758)
    - HR 6021—Federal Spending and Tax Expenditure Control Act (Box 16:, Folder 759)
    - HR 6021—Federal Spending and Tax Expenditure Control Act (Box 17:, Folder 760-764)
    - HR 6119—Advanced Automobile Propulsion (Box 17:, Folder 765)
    - HR 6380—Commission on More Effective Government (Box 17:, Folder 766)
    - HR 6476-6477—Recision Bills (Box 17:, Folder 767)
    - HR 6616 (Box 17:, Folder 768)
    - HR 7158 (Box 17:, Folder 769)
    - HR 7450—Monagan Federal Building (Box 17:, Folder 770)
    - HR 7482—Gold Medal, Olympic Team (Box 17:, Folder 771)
    - HR 7544—Robert N. Giaimo Federal Building (Box 17:, Folder 772)
    - HR 7765—Reconciliation Act (Box 17:, Folder 773)
    - HR 7816—Ribicoff Federal Building (Box 17:, Folder 774)
    - HR 8046—Independent Contractors Bill (Box 17:, Folder 775)
    - HR 8245—FDR Memorial at Warm Springs (Box 17:, Folder 776)
    - HR 8387—Immigration, Visas for Italian Earthquake Victims (Box 17:, Folder 777)
    - HConRes 107—First Budget Resolution FY80 (Box 17:, Folder 778)
    - HConRes 122—Peace in Ireland (Box 17:, Folder 779)
    - HConRes 138—Independent Audit of Oil Supplies (Box 17:, Folder 780)
    - HConRes 147—Baltic States (Box 17:, Folder 781)
    - HConRes 158—Philip Mazzei Stamp (Box 17:, Folder 782)
    - HConRes 186—Second Budget Resolution FY80 (Box 17:, Folder 783)
    - HConRes 200—Baltic States (Box 17:, Folder 784)
    - HConRes 212—Terminate Military Training for Iran (Box 17:, Folder 785)
    - HConRes 218—Use of Force if Necessary in Iran (Box 17:, Folder 786)
    - HConRes 245—Olympic Boycott (Box 17:, Folder 787)
    - HConRes 251—Andrei Sakharov (Box 17:, Folder 788)
    - HConRes 272 (Box 17:, Folder 789)
    - HConRes 307—First Budget Resolution FY81 (Box 17:, Folder 790)
    - HConRes 488—Revising the Congressional Budget (Box 17:, Folder 791)
    - HRes 8—Administration of Oath of Office to Stewart McKinney (Box 17:, Folder 792)
    - HRes 119-121—Budget Deferrals (Box 17:, Folder 793)
    - HRes 149—Alternate Site for Moscow Olympics (Box 17:, Folder 794)
    - HRes 220-221—Printing of Budget Documents (Box 17:, Folder 795)
    - HRes 235—Printing of Proceedings of Portrait of R.N. Giaimo (Box 17:, Folder 796)
    - HRes 360—See HRes 220 (Box 17:, Folder 797)
    - HRes 405—Scheduling of Committee Meetings (Box 17:, Folder 798)
    - HRes 412—Welcome for Pope John Paul II (Box 17:, Folder 799)
    - HRes 609—See HRes 220 (Box 17:, Folder 800)
    - HJRes 3—Will Rogers Day (Box 17:, Folder 801)
    - HJRes 68—National Family Week (Box 17:, Folder 802)
    - HJRes 69—Square Dancing (Box 17:, Folder 803)
    - HJRes 209—National Diabetes Week (Box 17:, Folder 804)
    - HJRes 244—National Grandparents Day (Box 17:, Folder 805)
    - HJRes 303—National Port Week (Box 17:, Folder 806)
    - HJRes 311—Queen Isabella Day (Box 17:, Folder 807)
    - HJRes 375—Victims of the Holocaust (Box 17:, Folder 808)
    - HJRes 385—500th Anniversary of Columbus' Voyage (Box 17:, Folder 809)
    - HJRes 389—National Rehabilitation Month (Box 17:, Folder 810)
    - HJRes 431—Vietnam Veterans Memorial Fund (Box 17:, Folder 811)
    - HJRes 442—National Athletic Boosters Week (Box 17:, Folder 812)
    - HJRes 447—Martin Luther King, Jr. Holiday (Box 17:, Folder 813)
    - HJRes 448—Second Resolution FY81 (Box 17:, Folder 814)
    - HJRes 463—National Diabetes Week (Box 17:, Folder 815)
    - HJRes 469—Iwo Jima Commemoration Day (Box 17:, Folder 816)
    - HJRes 470—Helen Keller Day (Box 17:, Folder 817)
    - HJRes 477—Walt Disney (Box 17:, Folder 818)
    - HJRes 551—National Port Week (Box 17:, Folder 819)
    - HJRes 564—National Italian-American Day (Box 17:, Folder 820)
    - HJRes 568—National Italian-American Heritage Week (Box 17:, Folder 821)
    - HJRes 584—250th Anniversary of Philip Mazzei's birth (Box 17:, Folder 822)
    - HJRes 594—Constantine Brumidi Day (Box 17:, Folder 823)
    - HJRes 629—Citizenship for Douglas C. Macintosh (Box 17:, Folder 824)
    - 96th Congress Legislative Summaries (Box 17:, Folder 825)
    - Cooley's Anemia (Box not specified)
      - Correspondence (Box 18:, Folder 826-829)
      - HR 14016 (Box 18:, Folder 830)
      - Projects (Box 18:, Folder 831-833)
      - Hearings (Box 18:, Folder 834)
      - HR 15474 (Box 18:, Folder 835)
    - HR 19037—Kennedy-Giaimo Reconversion (Box 18:, Folder 836)
    - HR 19037—Economic Conversion (Box 18:, Folder 837)
    - HR 34—Economic Conversion
      - Projects (Box 18:, Folder 838)
- Series III: Legislative Correspondence, 1973-1981
  - 93rd Congress, 1973-1974 (Box not specified)
    - General Legislation
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 839-840)
      - State Matter/No Jurisdiction (Box 19:, Folder 841)
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 842-843)
    - Arts and Humanities
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 844)
      - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities (Box 19:, Folder 845)
    - Civil Rights, Liberties, Constitutional Powers
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 846)
      - Amnesty (Box 19:, Folder 847-848)
      - House International Security Committee (Box 19:, Folder 849)
      - Indians (Box 19:, Folder 850)
      - Press Freedom (Box 19:, Folder 851)
    - Civil Rights, Liberties, Constitutional Powers
      - School Aid (Box 19:, Folder 852)
      - School Busing (Box 19:, Folder 853)
      - School Prayer (Box 19:, Folder 854)
    - Consumer Affairs, Product Safety
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 855-856)
      - Accuracy in Media (Box 19:, Folder 857)
      - Auto Safety and Regulations (Box 19:, Folder 858)
      - Product Reliability and Stability (Box 19:, Folder 859)
      - Truth in Packaging (Box 19:, Folder 860)
    - Defense and National Security
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 861)
    - Economy (Domestic)
      - General (Box 19:, Folder 862)
      - Commodity Shortage (Box 19:, Folder 863)
      - Connecticut, New Haven Economic Position (Box 19:, Folder 864)
      - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council (Box 19:, Folder 865)
      - Cost of Living Factors (Box 19:, Folder 866)
      - Economy, Food Prices (Box 19:, Folder 867)
      - Economy, Inflation (Box 19:, Folder 868-870)
      - Economy Stabilization (Box 19:, Folder 871)
      - Employment/Unemployment Problems (Box 19:, Folder 872)
      - Federal Employees (Box 19:, Folder 873)
      - Federal Spending/Budget (Box 19:, Folder 874)
      - Impoundment (Box 19:, Folder 875)
      - Minimum wage (Box 20:, Folder 876)
      - Price Commission Matters (Box 20:, Folder 877)
      - Wage and Price Control (Box 20:, Folder 878)
    - Education
      - General (Box 20:, Folder 879-880)
      - Elementary and Secondary Education (Box 20:, Folder 881)
      - Higher Education (Box 20:, Folder 882)
      - Libraries (Box 20:, Folder 883)
      - National Federation of the Blind (Box 20:, Folder 884)
      - Nursing Schools (Box 20:, Folder 885)
      - School Lunch Program (Box 20:, Folder 886)
      - Vocational Education (Box 20:, Folder 887)
    - Environment
      - General (Box 20:, Folder 888)
      - Animal Welfare (Box 20:, Folder 889-890)
      - Commercial Land Use (Box 20:, Folder 891-892)
      - Connecticut (Box 20:, Folder 893)
      - Connecticut Rivers and Waterways (Box 20:, Folder 894)
    - Environment
      - Energy Conservation (Box 20:, Folder 895)
      - Energy Resources and Gas Crisis (Box 20:, Folder 896-898)
      - Fuel Cost Adjustment Charge (Box 20:, Folder 899)
      - Land Management (Box 20:, Folder 900)
      - National Parks (Box 20:, Folder 901)
      - Pollution (Box 20:, Folder 902-904)
      - Solar Heating and Cooling Systems (Box 20:, Folder 905)
    - General Government
      - General (Box 20:, Folder 906-907)
      - Campaign Financing (Box 20:, Folder 908-910)
      - Commemorative Stamps (Box 20:, Folder 911)
      - Copyrights, Patents, Trademarks (Box 20:, Folder 912)
      - Election Reform (Box 21:, Folder 913-914)
      - Federal Employees (Box 21:, Folder 915)
      - Gerald Ford Confirmation (Box 21:, Folder 916)
      - Franking Privileges of Congress (Box 21:, Folder 917)
      - Impeachment (Box 21:, Folder 918-921)
      - Meskill Confirmation (Box 21:, Folder 922)
      - Monday Holiday Bill (Box 21:, Folder 923)
      - Nixon Pardon (Box 21:, Folder 924-925)
      - Postal Matters (Box 21:, Folder 926-927)
      - Presidential Immunity (Box 21:, Folder 928)
      - Questionnaires (Box 21:, Folder 929-930)
      - Reorganization Plan #2 (Box 21:, Folder 931)
      - Rockefeller Nomination (Box 21:, Folder 932)
      - Rocky Nomination (Box 21:, Folder 933)
      - Watergate Affair (Box 21:, Folder 934)
    - Health and Safety
      - General (Box 21:, Folder 935-936)
      - Diseases (Box 21:, Folder 937)
      - Drugs (Narcotics) (Box 21:, Folder 938)
      - Federal Health Programs (Box 21:, Folder 939)
      - Food and Drug Labeling (Box 21:, Folder 940-941)
      - Mental and Physical Retardation (Box 21:, Folder 942)
      - Occupational Safety (OSHA) (Box 21:, Folder 943)
      - Population Control (Box 21:, Folder 944-947)
    - House of Representatives, 1st Session (Box not specified)
      - Legislative Accomplishments of the 92nd Congress (Box 22:, Folder 948)
      - Legislative Accomplishments of the 93rd Congress (Box 22:, Folder 949)
      - Democratic Caucus
        - 1973 July 25 (Box 22:, Folder 950)
        - 1973 October 17 (Box 22:, Folder 951)
    - House of Representatives, 1st Session
      - Democratic Caucus
        - 1973 Rules (Box 22:, Folder 952-953)
      - Democratic Steering and Policy Committee
        - 4 December 1973 (Box 22:, Folder 954)
      - Democratic Caucus Subcommittee on Vice Presidential Selection (Box 22:, Folder 955)
      - DSG Housing Task Force (Box 22:, Folder 956)
      - Office of Science and Technology Assessments (Box 22:, Folder 957)
      - Standard of Official Conduct (Box 22:, Folder 958)
      - Whip Notices (Box 22:, Folder 959)
    - House of Representatives, 2nd Session
      - General (Box 22:, Folder 960)
      - Black Caucus (Box 22:, Folder 961)
      - Campaign Reform (Box 22:, Folder 962-963)
      - Coalition for a Democratic Majority (Box 22:, Folder 964-965)
      - Committee Assignments (Box 22:, Folder 966-967)
      - 94th Committee
        - Assignments/Nominees (Box 22:, Folder 968-969)
        - Assignments/Requests (Box 22:, Folder 970)
      - Democratic Members of Congress (Box 22:, Folder 971)
      - Democratic Party (Box 22:, Folder 972)
      - Democratic Steering and House Schedule (Box 22:, Folder 973)
      - Democratic Steering and Policy Committee/Resolution Economy (Box 22:, Folder 974)
      - Democratic Study Group (Box 22:, Folder 975)
      - House Leadership (Box 22:, Folder 976)
      - Internal Congressional Procedures/Rules (Box 22:, Folder 977)
      - New England Caucuses (Box 22:, Folder 978)
      - New England Congressional Caucus (Box 22:, Folder 979-981)
      - Select Committee on Committees (Box 23:, Folder 982-984)
    - Housing and City problems
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 985-987)
      - Flood Insurance (Box 23:, Folder 988)
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 23:, Folder 989)
    - International Relations
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 990)
      - Africa (Box 23:, Folder 991)
      - Asia (Box 23:, Folder 992)
      - Europe (Box 23:, Folder 993)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 23:, Folder 994)
      - Immigration (Box 23:, Folder 995)
      - Ireland (Box 23:, Folder 996)
    - International Relations
      - Israel (Box 23:, Folder 997)
      - Near East (Box 23:, Folder 998)
      - Nuclear Technology (Box 23:, Folder 999)
      - South America/Latin America (Box 23:, Folder 1000)
      - Soviet Union (Box 23:, Folder 1001)
      - United Nations (Box 23:, Folder 1002)
      - Vietnam
        - General (Box 23:, Folder 1003)
        - Post war aid (Box 23:, Folder 1004)
    - Judiciary Procedures
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 1005-1006)
      - Courts and Court Reform (Box 23:, Folder 1007)
      - Crime Legislation (Box 23:, Folder 1008)
      - Gun Control (Box 23:, Folder 1009)
      - Narcotics (Decriminalization) (Box 23:, Folder 1010)
      - Prison Reform (Box 23:, Folder 1011)
    - Labor/Management
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 1012-1013)
      - AFL-CIO Legislation and Attitudes (Box 23:, Folder 1014)
      - Collective Bargaining (Box 23:, Folder 1015)
      - Independent Business Ballots (Box 23:, Folder 1016)
      - Labor
        - Connecticut (Box 23:, Folder 1017)
        - National (Box 23:, Folder 1018)
      - National Right to Strike (Box 23:, Folder 1019)
      - National Right to Work (Box 23:, Folder 1020)
      - Strikes (Box 23:, Folder 1021)
    - Lobbyists/Pressure Groups
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 1022)
      - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA) (Box 23:, Folder 1023)
      - Common Cause (Box 23:, Folder 1024)
      - Industrial Groups (Box 23:, Folder 1025)
      - League of Women Voters (Box 23:, Folder 1026)
    - Poverty Programs
      - General (Box 23:, Folder 1027)
      - Community Programs (Box 23:, Folder 1028)
      - Food Stamps (Box 23:, Folder 1029)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 23:, Folder 1030)
    - Social Security (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 24:, Folder 1031-1032)
      - Disability Benefits (Box 24:, Folder 1033)
      - Earning Limitations (Box 24:, Folder 1034)
    - Social Security
      - Early Retirement (Box 24:, Folder 1035)
      - Elderly (Box 24:, Folder 1036)
      - HR 1 Questions (Health and Security Act) (Box 24:, Folder 1037)
      - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 24:, Folder 1038-1039)
      - National Health and Insurance (Box 24:, Folder 1040-1041)
      - Private Pensions (Box 24:, Folder 1042-1045)